Finding Aid for George Romney Papers 1920s-1973
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Romney Associates
  - Topical Files
    - Geneeral
      - Romney, George and position on issues
        - Federalism (Box 66-RA)
        - "Great Society" (Box 66-RA)
        - Lyndon Baines Johnson and Riots (Box 66-RA)
        - Labor (Box 66-RA)
        - Morals (Box 66-RA)
        - Public Demonstrations (Box 66-RA)
        - Religion (Box 66-RA)
        - Riots in Detroit (Box 66-RA)
        - States' Rights (Box 66-RA)
        - Tax Reform (Box 66-RA)
        - Traffic Safety (Box 66-RA)
        - "Tithe of Time" (Box 66-RA)
        - Welfare (Box 66-RA)
        - Youth (Box 66-RA)
      - Romney on the Record
        - 1957 (Box 66-RA)
        - 1960 (Box 66-RA)
        - 1961 (Box 66-RA)
        - 1963 (Box 66-RA)
        - 1964, 2 folders (Box 66-RA)
        - 1965 (Box 66-RA)
        - 1967 (Box 66-RA)
      - Science and Technology (Box 66-RA)
      - State File, 4 folders (Box 67-RA)
      - State of Michigan
        - General (Box 67-RA)
        - Advisory Commission on Local Government (Box 67-RA)
        - Elections
          - 1964 (Box 67-RA)
          - 1966, 2 folders (Box 67-RA)
        - Mackinac Republican Leadership Conference (Box 67-RA)
        - Population (Box 67-RA)
        - Republican Party (general) (Box 67-RA)
        - Republican State Convention 1967 (Box 67-RA)
        - Republican State Nationality Council (Box 67-RA)
        - Republican Student Leadership Conference 1966, 2 folders (Box 67-RA)
        - Republican West Central Organization, 2 folders (Box 67-RA)
        - Transportation Commission (Box 67-RA)
        - Urban (Box 67-RA)
      - Transportation
        - General (Box 67-RA)
        - Federal Aid Highways Act (Box 67-RA)
        - Mass transit (Box 67-RA)
        - Merchant marine (Box 67-RA)
        - Traffic safety (Box 67-RA)
      - Trips and other appearances, 27 folders (Box 67-RA)
      - Urban affairs, 1 folders; 1 volumes (Box 67-RA)
      - Welfare - Poverty
        - Great Society (Box 67-RA)
        - Guaranteed annual income (Box 67-RA)
        - Human Investment Act (Box 67-RA)
        - Medicare (Box 67-RA)
        - Negative Income Tax (Box 67-RA)
    - Topical Files (foreign affairs)
      - Files (Box 68-RA)
        (Contents not listed)
    - Topical Files (organizations)
      - Files: (Box 68-RA)
  - Clippings
    - Clippings arranged alphabetically by state (Box 69-RA)
    - Clippings arranged topically or by appearances (Box 70-RA)
    - Clippings arranged topically or by appearances (Box 71-RA)
  - Miscellaneous and campaign paraphernalia
    - Miscellaneous (Box 72-RA)
    - Campaign paraphernalia (Box 72-RA)